♪Looking in the mirror,
my temples have turned white♪
♪Taking off the hairpins and makeup,
shedding the disguise♪
♪A cold face♪
♪With two lines of tears♪
♪If an actor could gain pity♪
♪The audience offers sincere words♪
♪Perhaps the story could be changed♪
♪The storyteller says♪
♪This mortal world is full of turmoil♪
♪Within sight but beyond reach♪
♪Yet I still don't want to give up♪
♪Don't let the memory be hollowed out♪
♪Don't make me ridiculous♪
♪Some vows turn into smoke
and fade away♪
♪Even the leaves know when autumn comes,
but you don't even know me♪
♪Imprisoned in plight,
yet still full of passion♪
♪I mock this absurd and entangled love♪
♪How can I bear to let go♪
=Whispers of Southern Song=
=Episode 19=
Stop!
Governor, go!
What happened?
Xu Fan has retaken the Governor Mansion.
I fought while retreating,
and now the pursuers are not far behind.
There's no time.
Governor, go now!
What are you doing?
Governor, just leave me behind.
Yongnian!
I enlisted as a youth
and fought
over a dozen battles with you.
You've saved me
more times than I can count.
Saving you now is worth it all.
Yongnian.
Yongnian!
Open the door!
Go now!
Yongnian!
Young Marshal.
I'll go eavesdrop for you.
(Tomb of Revered Master Rong Huaiqiu)
A master for a day,
a grace for a lifetime.
Mr. Rong, do you want us
to dig up your ancestral grave?
Come on. Dig it up for me.
(Master, I hope you can forgive me.)
Mr. Rong,
open the box and let us check it out.
Mr. Du, how do you know
there are explosives in this box?
A bunch of cowards afraid to die.
(Master,)
(I'm unfilial.)
(But now I have no other choice.)
(I only hope you watch over Xu You'an
and Chun'er and let them live on.)
(To live on is hope.)
We have felt your sincerity, Mr. Rong.
Let's talk back at the chamber.
I can't believe you betrayed me
and betrayed everyone.
If it weren't to save you,
Yongnian wouldn't have died tragically.
But to save your own life,
you defected and became a traitor.
(Tomb of Revered Master Rong Huaiqiu)
Rong Xiaonan,
I would rather Zhuzi had died
eight years ago.
And you are not him.
Sir, a steamed bun.
A fried dough stick.
Miss Jiang.
Thank goodness I came in time.
Xu Fan's back in Governor Mansion
and has retaken military control.
He's put a city-wide bounty
on Xu You'an's head.
You must not go.
How could this happen?
No, I have to save him.
Miss, it's very dangerous
outside right now.
Let's go back to the mansion
and plan carefully.
Alright. Let's go.
What should I do?
Xu You'an has martial arts skills.
He'll surely be fine.
No, I have to find a way to help him.
The reward is a full hundred gold.
A handsome reward makes a brave man.
Miss, you're still engaged to him.
Will it implicate our Jiang family?
Hong'er, without him,
I would have been executed long ago.
Once the Jiang family falls,
we're just like driftwood in the chaos.
He is our lifesaver.
How can you not be grateful
but fear being implicated?
You may leave.
Are you alright?
Hurry, guard the door.
Come on.
Xu Fan has put
a city-wide bounty on your life.
What should we do?
To prevent Xu Fan
and the Xiaosheng Society from uniting,
we must first take out Xu Fan.
Otherwise, Xu Fan's next target
will be the Jiang family.
Where is Mr. Rong?
Didn't you go to save him?
Why didn't he come back?
To live, Rong Xiaonan surrendered
to the Xiaosheng Society.
From now on,
he has nothing to do with us anymore.
He wouldn't.
He's not that kind of person.
I saw it with my own eyes.
He led Du Xiaolin to dig up
Rongqing Troupe's memorial tomb.
He handed your mother's phoenix crown
straight to the Xiaosheng Society.
Impossible. He must have his reasons.
Where is he?
He's now an honored guest to Du Xiaolin.
He's at the Xiaosheng Society.
(Xiaosheng Society)
Mr. Rong.
Why exactly did you do that?
Miss Jiang, do you want to ask me
why I can come and go
from the Xiaosheng Society unscathed
and why I can command
the Xiaosheng Society's people?
Of course, it's to save my life.
By offering the kingfisher phoenix crown
and pledging allegiance to Mr. Du,
I can finally be someone of standing.
Otherwise, who would save me?
You, the nominal president
of the Chamber of Commerce?
Or Governor Xu, who lost his power
and became a stray dog?
Rong Xiaonan, you are heartless!
Miss Jiang, if you have time
to accuse me,
you'd be better off thinking
about how to save your family's legacy.
Those who conspire with the devil
will only meet their end.
Aren't you afraid they'll turn on you
once they've used you up?
Then Miss Jiang, you and Governor Xu
must protect yourselves well
and make sure you live long enough
to see me die.
♪As if it were fate♪
♪Deliberately playing tricks♪
♪We miss each other♪
♪Creating a turbulent drama♪
♪And a bizarre♪
♪Anonymous legend♪
♪The plot twists and turns♪
♪Play out over and over again♪
♪Waiting to be discarded♪
♪And you are like a moth to the flame♪
♪Refuse to submit♪
♪I can't bear to blame you♪
♪There are always too many♪
♪Helpless situations♪
♪Overwhelmed by time♪
♪Even if I have questions♪
♪I harbor desires♪
♪Nowhere to find answers♪
♪People come and go♪
♪I'm still all alone♪
♪Wandering around♪
♪Fortunate to have you with me♪
♪Go through the entanglement♪
♪If longing♪
♪Turns into dust and smoke♪
♪How can I be at ease♪
♪Having walked through prosperous times♪
♪And travelled around the world♪
♪Scars all over me♪
♪If longing never fades♪
♪Burns still hot♪
♪Let it turn into dust and smoke♪
♪After half a lifetime of loneliness♪
♪In the next life♪
♪Entangle with you again♪